No.
不
It can't be.
不可能
It isn't true.
这不是真的
Um, Twilight?
呃，暮光？
Twilight!
暮光！
The bus for Camp Everfree leaves in ten minutes!
去森灵营地的校车还有十分钟就要走了！
Oh no no no no no!
哦，不不不不！
I can't believe I overslept!
真不敢相信我睡过头了！
Me neither. That's not like you.
我也不信 这可不像你的作风
I know!
我知道！
Don't you have a super-annoying alarm clock that goes?
你不是有一个超级烦人的闹钟吗，就像是
It's gonna be fine.
没事的
We'll help you pack.
我们来帮你打包
Eh.
呃
We're gonna be out in the woods.
我们可是要待在森林里
When's she gonna need that?
她怎么会需要这个？
If we were going to the moon,
如果我们想玩得尽兴的话
I'd insist she'd pack an evening gown.
我就必须要坚持她带一套晚礼服
One never knows, darling.
指不定就用上了呢，亲爱的
Lemme just get changed.
让我先换件衣服
Midnight Sparkle?!
午夜闪闪？！
How is this possible?
这怎么可能？
Sunset Shimmer helped me defeat you at the Friendship Games!
余晖烁烁帮助我在友谊大赛中战胜了你！
You and your friends can never truly defeat me!
你和你的朋友们永远都不可能真正地战胜我！
Midnight Sparkle's a part of you!
午夜闪闪是你的一部分！
I'll always be there,
我会一直在你心底的
waiting in the darkest shadows of your mind!
最阴暗之处潜伏着的！
I'll be back, Twilight!
我会回来的，暮光！
And this time, I won't stop until I have all the magic!
这次，不得到所有的魔力我誓不罢休！
No!
不！
STOP!
停下！
Twilight, wake up!
暮光，醒醒！
We can't stop, silly!
我们不能停，小傻瓜！
We're not there yet!
我们还没到站呢！
Hey, are you okay?
嘿，你没事吧？
Heh. I'm fine.
恩，没事
We are gonna have so much fun!
我们会玩得很高兴的！
We're gonna roast marshmallows and eat marshmallows and sleep on marshmallow pillows!
我们要烤棉花糖然后吃棉花糖，然后枕着棉花糖睡觉！
Yeah, probably not gonna do that.
哈，八成不会这么做
Maybe you're not.
也许你不会！
Attention, students,
注意，同学们
we're almost there.
我们马上就要到目的地了
But before we arrive,
不过在此之前
we just wanted to say
我们只想说，
how proud we are of you for raising enough money
我们很骄傲能看到你们能筹足资金
to go on this class field trip.
来举行这次班级野外旅游
When we were your age, we made some of our favorite memories in these woods,
当我们还是你们这个年纪时，曾经在这片森林里留下了不少美好的回忆
and we're sure you will, too.
相信你们也会的
Now who's excited for Camp Everfree?!
现在告诉我谁对这次野营激动万分？！
Isn't Camp Everfree just beautiful?
森灵营地可真漂亮啊
Oh, I can't wait until we have our first nature walk.
噢，我都等不及进行我们的第一次野外徒步了
I definitely wanna go on one of those.
我也一直想来一次野外徒步
You wanna see all the adorable woodland creatures, too?
你也想见见那些可爱的森林动物们吗？
Yeah! Specifically squirrels!
是啊！尤其是松鼠！
More specifically, so I can chase 'em!
不过我其实更想追追它们呢！
I'm just lookin' forward to roughin' it.
我只是想来体验野外生活
I'm gonna make my own shelter, forage for food...
我要搭建我自己的庇护所，搜寻食物…
Uh, you know they provide us with food and tents, right?
呃，你知道他们会向我们提供帐篷和食物的，对吧？
Yup!
没错！
Still gonna forage though.
但我还是会去搜寻
I'm just after some R&R.
我就想放松放松
The past year has all been a bit too much for my taste.
这过去一年里出的事都快把我压垮了
I'll say!
可不是嘛！
We fought three evil sirens who tried to hypnotize everybody with their singing,
我们打败了三只企图用歌声催眠大家的海妖
one ridiculously competitive rival school,
一所想赢想疯了的学校
and two demon friends!
还交了两个恶魔朋友！
Uh, heh heh,
啊，哈哈
no offense.
无意冒犯
None taken.
没关系
You'll get used to it.
你会习惯的
Yep.
对
Canterlot High has become a regular magic magnet.
坎高这地方变得越来越招惹魔法了
Gonna be nice gettin' away to a place where we don't have to worry about that kinda stuff.
能到一个不用担心这种事的地方，真是太好了
Here you go, Twilight.
这个给你，暮光
Thanks.
谢了
It's Flash, right?
你是阿绅，对吧？
Yup, that's me!
对，是我！
And you're you.
而且你是你
And we don't know each other very well.
而且我们不太了解对方
Cool story, bro.
不错的故事，兄弟
Right.
恩
I guess I'll... see you around.
那么我先…回头见了
You know how there's that girl who looks just like you
你还记得有个和你长得一模一样
hen she's here but lives in another dimension and she's a pony princess?
住在另一个世界并且是个小马公主的女生吗
Uh-huh.
嗯哈
Flash kinda had a... thing for her.
阿绅对她…有点意思
Oh.
噢
Hey, everyone!
嗨，大家！
If you could start heading to the courtyard, that would be rad!
如果你们能朝院子这边走过来，可就再好不过了！
It's time to start the best week of camp ever!
是时候开始史上最棒露营周了！
Hi, everyone! Welcome to Camp Everfree!
大家好！欢迎来到森灵营地！
I'm Gloriosa Daisy, your camp director!
我是嘉兰金菊，你们的营长！
Think of me as your friendly camp and nature guide.
把我当做你们亲切和蔼的营地与大自然向导就好
And this is my brother, Timber Spruce!
这是我弟弟，云杉棕木！
Think of me as that awesome guy...
把我当成那种酷酷的
who should always be invited to fun things.
总是喜欢好玩的事情的那种人
We aim to please, so before we hand out our tent assignments,
为了你们能玩得舒心，在我们为你们分配帐篷之前
we'd like to hear from all of you.
我们想先听听你们的想法
You're free to do whatever you like here!
在这里，你们想干什么都可以！
Uh, except hike near the rock quarry.
啊，但是不能跑到采石场那边去
That's off-limits.
那里是禁区
Yes, but otherwise, your options are wide open.
对，不过除此之外，你们可以随便提出建议
So what activities will make this the very best week of your lives ever?
那么你们说什么样的活动才是最棒露营周所应该拥有的？
Ooh! Rock climbing!
噢！攀岩！
Done!
好！
Archery!
射箭！
Of course!
肯定的！
Tetherball!
绳球！
Naturally!
当然会有！
Rainbow, I know you're excited,
云宝，我知道你很兴奋
but maybe give somebody else a chance to make a suggestion.
但还是给别人一个说话的机会吧
Arts and crafts!
手工艺！
My mom... needs new pot holders.
我妈妈…需要新的锅垫
I'll supply the looms!
我会提供织布机！
Cookie decorating!
装饰饼干！
Ooh, I do make a mean sugar cookie.
我能做出不错的糖屑曲奇
Early morning nature walks?
清晨散步？
With walking sticks for everyone!
已经为大家准备好了手杖！
Ooh! Me! Oh, uh...
我！哦，呃…
a fashion show!
时装秀！
Where I design the most fabulous camp looks
我要根据当今最新的时尚潮流
inspired by today's hottest trends
来设计最漂亮的营地风格时装
and have them modeled by my classmates in a gorgeous outdoor setting!
然后让同学们作为模特来一场室外走秀！
A camp tradition!
露营传统！
We have literally never done that.
我们可真没搞过这种活动
I'll be taking requests the rest of the time you're here,
你们在这里如果有什么需求的话随时都可以告诉我
so if there's anything you'd like to do,
所以如果你们还想做什么别的活动
anything you need,
或者有什么需要
just ask.
尽管找我吧
What about the camp gift?
营地礼物呢？
That was my favorite Camp Everfree tradition.
那是我最喜欢的森灵营地传统
The camp gift! Of course!
营地礼物！当然了！
Really?
真的？
Yes, really.
对，真的
Well, I just thought-
啊，我只是想…
Then you thought wrong!
那你想错了！
Anyone else picking up on a little tension between Gloriosa and her brother?
有人注意到嘉兰和她弟弟之间有点不对劲吗？
Ehhh...
呃…
A little.
有点
Every year, campers work together to create something useful.
每一年，营员们都会一起制作一些有用的东西
A gift for future campers.
作为给未来营员的礼物
Working toward this common goal is key to forming the strong bonds
为这个共同目标而努力
that will last well beyond your time here at camp!
是你们之间形成牢固友谊的重要方式
Which is why it's so important.
所以这件事很重要
This gazebo was a gift from last year's group.
这个露台是去年队伍的礼物
Oh, oh, oh, and the totem pole
噢，噢，噢，还有图腾柱
and the sundial were also made by campers!
以及日晷也是由营员们制造的！
The sundial was our year's gift!
那日晷是我们那年的礼物！
Even though "some people" thought it was a little impractical,
虽然"某些人"觉得这有点不太实用
since the sundial can't be used at night.
毕竟日冕晚上不能用
Oh, you all seem like a-a really amazing group.
你们看上去是一支非常棒的团队
So I'm certain you'll come up with something inspiring to leave behind.
所以我相信你们肯定能留下些精彩的东西
Speaking of leaving things behind,
说到留下东西
now's the time when we give out tent assignments
我们应该给出帐篷的分配了
so you can leave your heavy bags behind.
这样你们好把行李都放好
Uh, girls will be getting their assignments from Timber.
恩，女生们到云杉棕木那里去领取分配
Guys, you're with me.
小伙子们跟我来
Oh, boy!
哦，天啊！
Yay! I'm in the Emerald Tent!
耶！我在绿宝石帐篷！
Ooh, me, too!
噢，我也是！
Aquamarine.
海蓝宝石
Me, too!
我也是！
Yee-hoo!
耶哈！
I got Amethyst.
我是紫水晶
Sapphire.
蓝宝石
Me, too!
我也是！
I mean, I'm assuming I am.
我是说，我认为我是
Technically, sapphires aren't just blue.
从理论上来说，蓝宝石可不只有蓝色的
They can be pink,
它们也可以是粉色
purple,
紫色
yellow...
黄色…
Yeah, but they're mostly blue.
对，但是它们大多是蓝色
That's why they're named after the Latin word sapphirus.
这就是为什么人们用拉丁文 sapphirus 来命名蓝宝石
That means "blue".
意思是，蓝色
I know.
我知道
But did you know that sapphires are just rubies without chromium?
不过你知不知道蓝宝石就是不含铬的红宝石？
No.
不知道
But did you know that Sapphire Tent is the best one?
不过你知不知道蓝宝石帐篷是最好的？
No.
不知道
Why's that?
为什么？
Because you're in it.
因为有你在
Oh, I bet you say that to all the campers.
噢，我打赌你对所有营员都这么说
Not true.
那可不一定
You're in the Ruby Tent?
你在红宝石帐篷？
Ha! That's the worst one!
哈！那是最差的！
Aw, man!
真倒霉！
I'm just jokin', buddy.
只是开个玩笑，伙计
Ruby Tent is great.
红宝石帐篷很棒
It's like a sapphire, but with chromium.
它就像蓝宝石，但是含有铬
But the Ruby and Coral Tents do look an awful lot alike to the undiscerning eye.
但红宝石帐篷和珊瑚帐篷对于不熟悉的人来说太像了
I better show you where it is.
我还是带你过去比较好
See ya around.
回见
What?
怎么？
Heh.
哈
Nothin'.
没事
That was adorable!
噢！真可爱！
Okay, everyone, go get settled in.
好了各位，安顿下来吧
We'll be meeting at the docks in fifteen minutes
十五分钟后我们在码头集合
to go over some camp safety rules.
学习野营安全守则！
Let me know if you need anything!
有什么需要的话就叫我吧！
I need somethin'.
我需要点东西
Filthy Rich!
臭钱！
So nice to see you.
很高兴见到你
What are you doing here?!
你在这干什么？
Camp is just getting started!
野营刚刚开始呢！
Just takin' in the scenery, Gloriosa Daisy.
只是四处看看风景 嘉兰金菊
It's so...
这很...
hmm...
嗯...
relaxin'.
让人放松
Well, you can look around when camp is over!
很好 你可以在野营结束后再继续看风景！
Now, if you don't mind...
如果现在你不介意的话...
Fine.
好吧
Filthy Rich is, uh, an alumni of the camp.
臭钱他，呃，当年也是营员
He likes to check on his old stomping grounds every now and again.
他喜欢时不时地来他以前驻扎的地方转转
But enough about him.
不过不说他了
Find your tents and put away your things.
找到你们的帐篷 放好东西
We've got the best week of camp ever to begin!
最棒露营周还在等着我们呢！
I'm all for learning safety rules,
我完全赞同学习安全规则
but I do hope I can get started on my designs for the camp fashion show sooner rather than later.
但我真希望我能尽早开始为野营时装秀准备设计
Huh. I still can't believe you talked Gloriosa into havin' a fashion show.
我还是不敢相信你竟然真的说服嘉兰举办时装秀了
We're in the middle of the woods, for cryin' out loud!
我们这可是在丛林腹地啊！
We're s'posed to be roughin' it!
我们应该粗野一点才对啊！
It's clear from Gloriosa's own wardrobe
从嘉兰的着装上来看
that she appreciates a well put together look.
她显然也是喜欢看漂亮衣服的那类人
Even if we are in the "middle of the woods".
哪怕是我们在这“丛林腹地”里
Fair enough.
算你有理
Just as long as you don't put me in one of your fancy pants outfits.
只要你别给我穿你那些稀奇古怪的东西就行
You're gonna, aren't ya?
你打算这么做，是吧？
No.
不会
Yes! Don't worry, darling.
才怪！别担心
It'll absolutely speak to your personal sense of style...
我给你的衣服绝对符合你的审美观…
That was weird back there, right?
刚刚那会儿很奇怪对吧？
With that guy, Filthy Rich?
就那家伙，臭钱？
Huh?
是吗？
Oh. Uh, I guess so.
哦，呃，我猜是吧
I just have this feeling that Gloriosa's hiding something.
我只是感觉嘉兰在隐瞒什么
Her brother is pretty cute, though, huh?
不过她弟人不错啊，对吧
He's okay.
他还行吧
Ooooh,
噢
now look who's trying to hide something!
有人想要隐瞒些什么哦！
No, I'm not!
不 我才没有！
Hey, you okay?
喂 你还好吗？
You seemed a little freaked out on the bus earlier.
你刚刚在巴士上看起来吓坏了
Probably had another one of her nightmares.
她大概又做了个噩梦吧
I'm fine.
我没事
I mean, what do I have to complain about?
毕竟 我有什么好烦心的呢？
Ever since I transferred here,
自从我转到坎高这边
everyone from CHS has been really nice and accepting,
学校里的各位都接纳了我，我与大家相处也很融洽
especially considering what happened at the Friendship Games.
即便我在友谊大赛上做了那些事情
That wasn't your fault.
那不是你的错
Principal Cinch is the one who encouraged you to try and use all that magic to win the Games for Crystal Prep.
是严校长促使你尝试那些魔法来帮助水晶预科获取大赛胜利
You weren't ready to have that kind of power.
你还没准备好去承受那种魔力
But it's over now.
但那都已经过去了
And if there's any group that's gonna forgive you for something that happened in the past,
如果非要问会有什么人能原谅你的过错的话
trust me, it's this one.
相信我，那就是大家
You guys comin' or what?
你们磨蹭什么呢？
Be right there!
马上来！
I just wanna put on some sunscreen.
我想擦点防晒霜
Huh. I Coulda sworn I packed it.
哈？我明明记得带了来着
Found it!
找到啦！